DO YOU STAND BY THAT STATEMENT TODAY? DIR.
DO YOU STAND BY THAT STATEMENT TODAY? DIR. PATEL:
DO YOU STAND BY THAT STATEMENT TODAY? DIR. PATEL: YES.
TODAY? DIR. PATEL: YES.
TODAY? DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN.
TODAY? DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN. BOOKER:
TODAY? DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN. BOOKER: HAVE
TODAY? DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN. BOOKER: HAVE YOU
TODAY? DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN. BOOKER: HAVE YOU EVER
TODAY? DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN. BOOKER: HAVE YOU EVER MADE
DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN. BOOKER: HAVE YOU EVER MADE
DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN. BOOKER: HAVE YOU EVER MADE A
DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN. BOOKER: HAVE YOU EVER MADE A FALSE
DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN. BOOKER: HAVE YOU EVER MADE A FALSE STATEMENT
DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN. BOOKER: HAVE YOU EVER MADE A FALSE STATEMENT BEFORE
DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN. BOOKER: HAVE YOU EVER MADE A FALSE STATEMENT BEFORE A
DIR. PATEL: YES. SEN. BOOKER: HAVE YOU EVER MADE A FALSE STATEMENT BEFORE A GRAND
SEN. BOOKER: HAVE YOU EVER MADE A FALSE STATEMENT BEFORE A GRAND
SEN. BOOKER: HAVE YOU EVER MADE A FALSE STATEMENT BEFORE A GRAND JURY?
A FALSE STATEMENT BEFORE A GRAND JURY?
A FALSE STATEMENT BEFORE A GRAND JURY? DIR.
A FALSE STATEMENT BEFORE A GRAND JURY? DIR. PATEL:
A FALSE STATEMENT BEFORE A GRAND JURY? DIR. PATEL: NOPE.
JURY? DIR. PATEL: NOPE.
JURY? DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN.
JURY? DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN. BOOKER:
JURY? DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR
JURY? DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON
JURY? DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY
JURY? DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY 12
DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY 12
DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY 12 OF
DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY 12 OF THIS
DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY 12 OF THIS YEAR,
DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY 12 OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE
DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY 12 OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE THE
DIR. PATEL: NOPE. SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY 12 OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE THE SENATE
SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY 12 OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE THE SENATE
SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY 12 OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE THE SENATE APPROPRIATIONS
SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY 12 OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE THE SENATE APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE,
SEN. BOOKER: DIRECTOR ON MAY 12 OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE THE SENATE APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU
OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE THE SENATE APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU
OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE THE SENATE APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU TESTIFIED,
OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE THE SENATE APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU TESTIFIED, AND
OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE THE SENATE APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU TESTIFIED, AND I'M
OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE THE SENATE APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING
OF THIS YEAR, BEFORE THE SENATE APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU,
APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU,
APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU, I
APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU, I CAN
APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU, I CAN TELL
APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU, I CAN TELL YOU
APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE, YOU TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU, I CAN TELL YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY
TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU, I CAN TELL YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY
TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU, I CAN TELL YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY THIS
TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU, I CAN TELL YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY THIS FBI
TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU, I CAN TELL YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY THIS FBI IS
TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU, I CAN TELL YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY THIS FBI IS TARGETING
TESTIFIED, AND I'M QUOTING YOU, I CAN TELL YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY THIS FBI IS TARGETING AND
I CAN TELL YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY THIS FBI IS TARGETING AND
I CAN TELL YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY THIS FBI IS TARGETING AND INVESTIGATING
I CAN TELL YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY THIS FBI IS TARGETING AND INVESTIGATING NO
I CAN TELL YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY THIS FBI IS TARGETING AND INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS,
THIS FBI IS TARGETING AND INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS,
THIS FBI IS TARGETING AND INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS, EN
THIS FBI IS TARGETING AND INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS, END
THIS FBI IS TARGETING AND INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS, END QUOTE.
INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS, END QUOTE.
INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS, END QUOTE. BUT
INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS, END QUOTE. BUT IN
INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS, END QUOTE. BUT IN MARCH
INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS, END QUOTE. BUT IN MARCH OF
INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS, END QUOTE. BUT IN MARCH OF THIS
INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS, END QUOTE. BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR,
INVESTIGATING NO JOURNALISTS, END QUOTE. BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER
END QUOTE. BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER
END QUOTE. BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH
END QUOTE. BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON
END QUOTE. BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON O
END QUOTE. BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF
END QUOTE. BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE
END QUOTE. BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW
BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW
BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW YORK
BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW YORK TIMES
BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW YORK TIMES REPORTED
BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW YORK TIMES REPORTED IT
BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND
BUT IN MARCH OF THIS YEAR, AFTER ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND USED
ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND USED
ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND USED FULL-TIME
ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND USED FULL-TIME FBI
ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND USED FULL-TIME FBI SWAT
ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND USED FULL-TIME FBI SWAT DETAIL
ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON OF THE NEW YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND USED FULL-TIME FBI SWAT DETAIL TO
YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND USED FULL-TIME FBI SWAT DETAIL TO
YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND USED FULL-TIME FBI SWAT DETAIL TO PROTECT
YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND USED FULL-TIME FBI SWAT DETAIL TO PROTECT AND
YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND USED FULL-TIME FBI SWAT DETAIL TO PROTECT AND DRIVE
YORK TIMES REPORTED IT AND USED FULL-TIME FBI SWAT DETAIL TO PROTECT AND DRIVE YOUR
FULL-TIME FBI SWAT DETAIL TO PROTECT AND DRIVE YOUR
FULL-TIME FBI SWAT DETAIL TO PROTECT AND DRIVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND
FULL-TIME FBI SWAT DETAIL TO PROTECT AND DRIVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
FULL-TIME FBI SWAT DETAIL TO PROTECT AND DRIVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND, YOUR
FULL-TIME FBI SWAT DETAIL TO PROTECT AND DRIVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND, YOUR AGENTS
PROTECT AND DRIVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND, YOUR AGENTS
PROTECT AND DRIVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND, YOUR AGENTS ATTRIBUTE
PROTECT AND DRIVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND, YOUR AGENTS ATTRIBUTE YOUR
PROTECT AND DRIVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND, YOUR AGENTS ATTRIBUTE YOUR GIRLFRIEND
PROTECT AND DRIVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND, YOUR AGENTS ATTRIBUTE YOUR GIRLFRIEND ABOUT
GIRLFRIEND, YOUR AGENTS ATTRIBUTE YOUR GIRLFRIEND ABOUT
GIRLFRIEND, YOUR AGENTS ATTRIBUTE YOUR GIRLFRIEND ABOUT MS.
GIRLFRIEND, YOUR AGENTS ATTRIBUTE YOUR GIRLFRIEND ABOUT MS. WILLIAMSON'S
GIRLFRIEND, YOUR AGENTS ATTRIBUTE YOUR GIRLFRIEND ABOUT MS. WILLIAMSON'S REPORTING.
ATTRIBUTE YOUR GIRLFRIEND ABOUT MS. WILLIAMSON'S REPORTING.
ATTRIBUTE YOUR GIRLFRIEND ABOUT MS. WILLIAMSON'S REPORTING. IS
ATTRIBUTE YOUR GIRLFRIEND ABOUT MS. WILLIAMSON'S REPORTING. IS THAT
ATTRIBUTE YOUR GIRLFRIEND ABOUT MS. WILLIAMSON'S REPORTING. IS THAT TRUE?
MS. WILLIAMSON'S REPORTING. IS THAT TRUE?
MS. WILLIAMSON'S REPORTING. IS THAT TRUE? DIR.
MS. WILLIAMSON'S REPORTING. IS THAT TRUE? DIR. PATEL:
MS. WILLIAMSON'S REPORTING. IS THAT TRUE? DIR. PATEL: WHY
MS. WILLIAMSON'S REPORTING. IS THAT TRUE? DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE
MS. WILLIAMSON'S REPORTING. IS THAT TRUE? DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU
MS. WILLIAMSON'S REPORTING. IS THAT TRUE? DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING
IS THAT TRUE? DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING
IS THAT TRUE? DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT
IS THAT TRUE? DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THAT
IS THAT TRUE? DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THAT THREAT?
DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THAT THREAT?
DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THAT THREAT? SEN.
DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THAT THREAT? SEN. BOOKER:
DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THAT THREAT? SEN. BOOKER: IT
DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THAT THREAT? SEN. BOOKER: IT IS
DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THAT THREAT? SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A
DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THAT THREAT? SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES
DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THAT THREAT? SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR
DIR. PATEL: WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT THAT THREAT? SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR NO
ABOUT THAT THREAT? SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR NO
ABOUT THAT THREAT? SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR NO QUESTION.
SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR NO QUESTION.
SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR NO QUESTION. DIR.
SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR NO QUESTION. DIR. PATEL:
SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR NO QUESTION. DIR. PATEL: I
SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR NO QUESTION. DIR. PATEL: I AM
SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR NO QUESTION. DIR. PATEL: I AM NOT
SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR NO QUESTION. DIR. PATEL: I AM NOT GOING
SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR NO QUESTION. DIR. PATEL: I AM NOT GOING T
SEN. BOOKER: IT IS A YES OR NO QUESTION. DIR. PATEL: I AM NOT GOING TO
QUESTION. DIR. PATEL: I AM NOT GOING TO
QUESTION. DIR. PATEL: I AM NOT GOING TO ANSWER
QUESTION. DIR. PATEL: I AM NOT GOING TO ANSWER IT.
DIR. PATEL: I AM NOT GOING TO ANSWER IT.
DIR. PATEL: I AM NOT GOING TO ANSWER IT. SEN.
DIR. PATEL: I AM NOT GOING TO ANSWER IT. SEN. BOOKER:
DIR. PATEL: I AM NOT GOING TO ANSWER IT. SEN. BOOKER: THAT
DIR. PATEL: I AM NOT GOING TO ANSWER IT. SEN. BOOKER: THAT HIS
ANSWER IT. SEN. BOOKER: THAT HIS
ANSWER IT. SEN. BOOKER: THAT HIS AFFIRMATION.
SEN. BOOKER: THAT HIS AFFIRMATION.
SEN. BOOKER: THAT HIS AFFIRMATION. YOUR
SEN. BOOKER: THAT HIS AFFIRMATION. YOUR AGENTS
SEN. BOOKER: THAT HIS AFFIRMATION. YOUR AGENTS RENT
SEN. BOOKER: THAT HIS AFFIRMATION. YOUR AGENTS RENT ELIZABETH
AFFIRMATION. YOUR AGENTS RENT ELIZABETH
AFFIRMATION. YOUR AGENTS RENT ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON'S
AFFIRMATION. YOUR AGENTS RENT ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON'S NAME
AFFIRMATION. YOUR AGENTS RENT ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO
AFFIRMATION. YOUR AGENTS RENT ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO FEDERAL
YOUR AGENTS RENT ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO FEDERAL
YOUR AGENTS RENT ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO FEDERAL DATABASES
YOUR AGENTS RENT ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO FEDERAL DATABASES TO
YOUR AGENTS RENT ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO FEDERAL DATABASES TO GATHER
YOUR AGENTS RENT ELIZABETH WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO FEDERAL DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION
WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO FEDERAL DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION
WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO FEDERAL DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION ABOUT
WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO FEDERAL DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION ABOUT HER,
WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO FEDERAL DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION ABOUT HER, YES
WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO FEDERAL DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION ABOUT HER, YES OR
WILLIAMSON'S NAME TO FEDERAL DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION ABOUT HER, YES OR NO?
DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION ABOUT HER, YES OR NO?
DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION ABOUT HER, YES OR NO? DIR.
DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION ABOUT HER, YES OR NO? DIR. PATEL:
DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION ABOUT HER, YES OR NO? DIR. PATEL: YOU
DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION ABOUT HER, YES OR NO? DIR. PATEL: YOU CAN
DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION ABOUT HER, YES OR NO? DIR. PATEL: YOU CAN SAY
DATABASES TO GATHER INFORMATION ABOUT HER, YES OR NO? DIR. PATEL: YOU CAN SAY WHATEVER
ABOUT HER, YES OR NO? DIR. PATEL: YOU CAN SAY WHATEVER
ABOUT HER, YES OR NO? DIR. PATEL: YOU CAN SAY WHATEVER LIES
ABOUT HER, YES OR NO? DIR. PATEL: YOU CAN SAY WHATEVER LIES YOU
ABOUT HER, YES OR NO? DIR. PATEL: YOU CAN SAY WHATEVER LIES YOU WANT.
DIR. PATEL: YOU CAN SAY WHATEVER LIES YOU WANT.
DIR. PATEL: YOU CAN SAY WHATEVER LIES YOU WANT. I
DIR. PATEL: YOU CAN SAY WHATEVER LIES YOU WANT. I WILL
DIR. PATEL: YOU CAN SAY WHATEVER LIES YOU WANT. I WILL NOT
DIR. PATEL: YOU CAN SAY WHATEVER LIES YOU WANT. I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE.
LIES YOU WANT. I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE.
LIES YOU WANT. I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE. SEN.
LIES YOU WANT. I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER:
LIES YOU WANT. I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: LIE?
I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: LIE?
I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: LIE? YOU
I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: LIE? YOU ARE
I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: LIE? YOU ARE SAYING
I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: LIE? YOU ARE SAYING THAT
I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: LIE? YOU ARE SAYING THAT IS
I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: LIE? YOU ARE SAYING THAT IS NOT
I WILL NOT PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: LIE? YOU ARE SAYING THAT IS NOT A
SEN. BOOKER: LIE? YOU ARE SAYING THAT IS NOT A
SEN. BOOKER: LIE? YOU ARE SAYING THAT IS NOT A FACT?
YOU ARE SAYING THAT IS NOT A FACT?
YOU ARE SAYING THAT IS NOT A FACT? DIR.
YOU ARE SAYING THAT IS NOT A FACT? DIR. PATEL:
YOU ARE SAYING THAT IS NOT A FACT? DIR. PATEL: STOP
YOU ARE SAYING THAT IS NOT A FACT? DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING
YOU ARE SAYING THAT IS NOT A FACT? DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING ME
FACT? DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING ME
FACT? DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING ME AND
FACT? DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING ME AND MY
FACT? DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING ME AND MY LOVED
FACT? DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING ME AND MY LOVED ONES.
DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING ME AND MY LOVED ONES.
DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING ME AND MY LOVED ONES. WE
DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING ME AND MY LOVED ONES. WE HAVE
DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING ME AND MY LOVED ONES. WE HAVE SEEN
DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING ME AND MY LOVED ONES. WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE
DIR. PATEL: STOP ATTACKING ME AND MY LOVED ONES. WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE PEOPLE
AND MY LOVED ONES. WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE PEOPLE
AND MY LOVED ONES. WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE PEOPLE THREATEN
AND MY LOVED ONES. WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE PEOPLE THREATEN OUR
AND MY LOVED ONES. WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE PEOPLE THREATEN OUR LIVES
AND MY LOVED ONES. WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE PEOPLE THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED
AND MY LOVED ONES. WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE PEOPLE THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON
AND MY LOVED ONES. WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE PEOPLE THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON THIS
WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE PEOPLE THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON THIS
WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE PEOPLE THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON THIS LINE
WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE PEOPLE THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON THIS LINE OF
WE HAVE SEEN MULTIPLE PEOPLE THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON THIS LINE OF ATTACK.
THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON THIS LINE OF ATTACK.
THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON THIS LINE OF ATTACK. I
THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON THIS LINE OF ATTACK. I AM
THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON THIS LINE OF ATTACK. I AM NOT
THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON THIS LINE OF ATTACK. I AM NOT GOING
THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON THIS LINE OF ATTACK. I AM NOT GOING TO
THREATEN OUR LIVES BASED ON THIS LINE OF ATTACK. I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE.
LINE OF ATTACK. I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE.
LINE OF ATTACK. I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN.
LINE OF ATTACK. I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER:
LINE OF ATTACK. I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN,
LINE OF ATTACK. I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I
LINE OF ATTACK. I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM
I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM
I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING
I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING YES
I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING YES O
I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING YES OR
I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING YES OR NO
I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS
I AM NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE. SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT
SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT
SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT ACTIVITIES
SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT ACTIVITIES O
SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT ACTIVITIES OF
SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT ACTIVITIES OF THE
SEN. BOOKER: CHAIRMAN, I AM ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI.
ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI.
ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI. IT
ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI. IT IS
ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI. IT IS A
ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI. IT IS A MATTER
ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI. IT IS A MATTER OF
ASKING YES OR NO QUESTIONS ABOUT ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI. IT IS A MATTER OF OVERSIGHT.
ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI. IT IS A MATTER OF OVERSIGHT.
ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI. IT IS A MATTER OF OVERSIGHT. I
ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI. IT IS A MATTER OF OVERSIGHT. I HAVE
ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI. IT IS A MATTER OF OVERSIGHT. I HAVE A
ACTIVITIES OF THE FBI. IT IS A MATTER OF OVERSIGHT. I HAVE A RIGHT.
IT IS A MATTER OF OVERSIGHT. I HAVE A RIGHT.
IT IS A MATTER OF OVERSIGHT. I HAVE A RIGHT. CHAIR
IT IS A MATTER OF OVERSIGHT. I HAVE A RIGHT. CHAIR DURBIN:
IT IS A MATTER OF OVERSIGHT. I HAVE A RIGHT. CHAIR DURBIN: NORMALLY,
IT IS A MATTER OF OVERSIGHT. I HAVE A RIGHT. CHAIR DURBIN: NORMALLY, I
IT IS A MATTER OF OVERSIGHT. I HAVE A RIGHT. CHAIR DURBIN: NORMALLY, I WOULD
I HAVE A RIGHT. CHAIR DURBIN: NORMALLY, I WOULD